Ismay, Lou; Papers ua902.064
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Files, 1969-1977; Undated; 3; 1.33 cubic ft.
  - Faculty and Pay Rate, 1969-1972 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Fiser, Webb, Littlefield, T.H., Schaefer, Vincent A., College of Environmental Studies of SUNYA, 1970 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Grant Preamble, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Interagency, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - Jobs, 1968; 1972; 1974 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - Jobs, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - The Legislative Seminar, 1975 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - Luce Foundation Institutes Professorship Program, 1969 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - "Man and His Environment", Edward Renshaw Curriculum, 1970 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - Pre-Registration, 1974 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 39)
  - The Proposal: by the Pilot Group of Experimental College, Undated (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 40)
  - Proposals for Programs and Faculty, 1971; 1972; 1973 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 41)
  - Records Management, 1976 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 42)
  - Registration, 1974 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 43)
  - Registration 1975, Summer 1976 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 44)
  - Resumes, Undated (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Review of Environmental Studies Program, 1975 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Schedule of Classes, Summer 1974 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Schedule of Classes at the University at Albany, Fall 1976 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Staff Beat, 1969 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Staff Salaries, 1975 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Student Suggestions For Environmental Workshop, Undated (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Student Suggestions For Faculty, Undated (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Subjects and Professors, 1970 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Summer 1977 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Summer Sessions Catalog, 1974 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - SUNY At Albany Telephone Directory, Undated (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - SUNYA Bill: The Second Field -- An Interpretation, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - SUNYA Courses Related to the Environment, Spring 1972 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - SUNYA Faculty Handbook, Undated (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - SUNYA Library, 1970 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Undergraduate Degree Requirements, 1970 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate Research Participation, Undated (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - University at Albany: Mission, Programs, & Priorities for Action, 1977 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - University Senate and Decisions, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
- Student Writings, 1969-1977; Undated; 4; 11.75 cubic ft.
  The projects of students in the Environmental Forum that were kept by Lou Ismay can be found in this series. The projects are filed in alphabetical order by name of student. Journals, student papers, student project reports, and student autobiographies are part of this series. The papers are on a range of environmental issues with many relating to recycling and other relevant projects done around campus and the Capital Region. Photographs and slides that accompany student papers were kept together with the papers. Oversized material is filed separately and includes 4 posters and other oversized projects. Audiovisuals for student projects are also in the series, including 11 audiocassette tapes and 1 reel-to-reel audiotape.
  This series is restricted.
  - Abelson, Rena, A Play, 1971 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - Abrams, Brian, Abraxas Magazine, 1971 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - Abrams, Brian, untitled, Undated (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Abrams, Marla, Carcinogenic Agents in Drinking Water, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Abrams, Marla, Journal, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)
  - Adamowicz, Anne Marie and Mattimore, Marianne, A Study on Cosmetics, 1971 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Ackermann, Elizabeth Climate and the Worlds Food Supply, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - Ackermann, Elizabeth, untitled, Undated (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - Ahl, Peter, untitled, Undated (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Albert, Janet, No Fault Insurance for NYS: A Social Issue, 1972 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)
  - Aldrich, Andy, Aspects of change in Art and Nature, 1973 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Aldrich, Andy, Transcending Structuring, 1974 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12)
  - Allard, David, Town of North Greenbush Environmental Conservation Council, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 13)
  - Allen, Barbara; Duff, Robert, Noise in the City of Albany, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 14)
  - Allsop, Richard, Journal, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 15)
  - Allsop, Richard, Velikovsky and Science, Undated (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 16)
  - Alpert, Fredda; Legislative Internship NYPIRG, 1974 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 17)
  - Alpert, Fredda, NYPIRG, 1974 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 18)
  - Anderson Gail; Durkot, David, The Town of Guilderland's Water Quality Improvement Project, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 19)
  - Anderson, Kathy, Resource Recovery, Undated (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 20)
  - Anderson, Kathy, Journal, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 21)
  - Andres, John, Letter to Jimmy Carter, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 22)
  - Applebaum, Bruce, untitled, Undated (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 23)
  - Armonia, Denise, An Annotated Bibliography of Children's Books Dealing with Environmental Consciousness, 1974 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 24)
  - Aschenbrand, Mark; Myers, Carol; Zif, Robert, Redecoration of Eastman Towers Twelth Floor Lounge, Undated (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 25)
  - Atkinson, Pam, The Why Don't "They" Syndrome and How People Morally Justify Environmental Destruction, 1972 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 26)
  - Auelair, Philippe, Melanin, Undated (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 27)
  - Autobiographies, 1970 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 28-29)
  - Autobiographies, 1971 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 30-31)
  - Autobiographies, 1972 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 32)
  - Autobiographies, 1973 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 33-35)
  - Autobiographies, 1974 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 36-37)
  - Autobiographies, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 38)
  - Autobiographies, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 39)
  - Autobiographies, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 40)
  - Avner, Judy; Brodsky, Joanne; Mayock, Ellen, Environmental Legislation Study Group, Undated (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 41)
  - Axelrod, Bennet, Tree Planting, 1973 (Box 1 (4-Student Writings), Folder 42)
  - Babineau, David; Gordon, Ruth; Bessette, Donald, What is Water Pollution?, 1971 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - Balluff, David, A Survey on Returnable Bottles, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - Baltrushis, Joe, regional Project, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Barber, Ed; Hood, Chuck, untitled, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Barnett, Fran, The Television as a Tool for Environmental Education, 1977 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)
  - Bass, Deborah, Journal, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Bauer, Douglas, Air Pollution, 1972 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - Baxter, Robert, The American Indians Struggle to Regain lost Rights, 1973 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - Becraft, David; Rosengarten, Ronald, A Study of Automobile Waste Oil in Albany, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Beerle, Sandi, Final, 1976 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)
  - Beevers, Donald, A Method of defining RRRC IV and V Recreational Land as an example of Environmental Planning, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Behan, Mike, Narcotics and the Law, 1972 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12)
  - Belm, Ralf, A handbook for submitting Legislation to the New York State Legislature, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 13)
  - Bender, Roger, Cruel and Unusual Punishment; Past and Present, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 14)
  - Benkart, Pam, Journal The NY Environmental News, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 15)
  - Benkart, Pam; Okrent, Bill, Recycling at State Quad, 1972 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 16)
  - Berezow, Mark, New York's proposed bottle Bill and Its Implications, 1977 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 17)
  - Berkery, Bob, untitled, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 18)
  - Berliner, Guy, University Food Waste as Compared to World Shortage, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 19)
  - Bernstein, Bill; Dionne, Glenn; Slutzky, Gary, untitled, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 20)
  - Bertaccini, David, Exam, 1977 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 21)
  - Bertaccini, David, Journal, Waterways, 1976 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 22)
  - Bewsher, J. Michael, untitled, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 23)
  - Biittner, Brian, The Role of NY State in Planning and Controlling on Shore Activities, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 24)
  - Biittner, Brian; Cramer, Kathy, Albany, County Environmental Management Council Wetlands Inventory, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 25)
  - Bisgeier, Risa, Exam book, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 26)
  - Black, James, untitled, 1976 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 27)
  - Blais, Peter; Warren, Cynthia, A Study of the Feasibility of the Cafeteria, 1971 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 28)
  - Blank, Barbara; Mann, Linda; Simon, Fred, Hillside Show, 1971 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 29)
  - Blatt, Ronald, "Econotes", 1976 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 30)
  - Blecher, Nina, Hazards of a Dental Office, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 31)
  - Blitstein, Dianne, Lead Poisoning Prevention, 1971 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 32)
  - Bluestein, R.A., Misuse Air, Land, Water, 1973 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 33)
  - Bodane, Richard, Exam Book, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 34)
  - Bodner, Sandra, on Health, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 35)
  - Bonchonsky, Larry, High Technology Companies and a Societal Environmental Ramification Factor, 1976 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 36)
  - Bonchonsky, Michael, The Evaluation of Wetlands, 1971 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 37)
  - Bonchonsky, Peter, New York State Legislature, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 38)
  - bonenfant, R.J., An Honorable Press -- A Responsible Government, 1973 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 39)
  - Bourger, Vivienne; Schwartz, Steven, Water Pollution Study, 1976 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 40)
  - Bradbury, Robert, untitled, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 41)
  - Bradley, Brian, Wastewater Treatment for Rensselaer, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 42)
  - Braaten, Richard, The Bishoppe Processing Co. v. The Environmental Protection Agency, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 43)
  - Brandwein, Mark, The Albany County Nature and Historic Preserve Law, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 44)
  - Brate, Marie; Goodman, Pamela; Roizen, Stephen, It's All One, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 45)
  - Braunlich, Darlys, Journal, 1974 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 46)
  - Braverman, Mark, Noise Pollution, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 47)
  - Bray, Larry, Evan, Pure Drinking Water, 1977 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 48)
  - Bray, Larry Evan, The Salting of our Roads, 1977 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 49)
  - Bresky, Marc, High Level Radioactive, Waste Management Alternatives, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 50)
  - Brickman, Robert, Exam book, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 51)
  - Brickman, Robert, Prospects for Weather Modification, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 52)
  - Brower, Mark, Instituting an Aluminum Recycling Program, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 53)
  - Brown, George, Shaker Communities, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 54)
  - Brown, Peter, A Water Quality Study of the Patroon Creek, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 55)
  - Bruschi, Damian, Macrobiotics: An Answer for Humanity, 1977 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 56)
  - Bruso, Robert, Blenheim Gilboa Hydroelectric Project, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 57)
  - Bryant, Estelle, The Effects of Marijuana, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 58)
  - Bryton, Benjamin, A Study in Poetry of man's Contract for a friend, 1971 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 59)
  - Bukalt, Mary Anne, Issues, Legislation and Administration in Nuclear Reactor Siting, 1977 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 60)
  - Bunis, Nancy, regarding; A week with Asimov, Undated (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 61)
  - Burgess, Lynn, Environmental Law, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 62)
  - Butterman, David, The Freshwater Snails of Central New York as a Nutrient Source, 1977 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 63)
  - The Effect of Gasoline upon two Freshwater Mollusks, 1976 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 64)
  - Byrns, Carol, The Effect of Organochlorine Pesticides Wildlife, 1976 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 65)
  - Byrns, Carol, Independent Studies, 1977 (Box 2 (4-Student Writings), Folder 66)
  - Call, Philip, Racial Legislation and some of its Problems, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - Canale, David, The Wage-Price Freeze, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - Canter, Robert, The Effect of Architecture upon Social Interaction at the Dormitories at SUNY At Albany, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Caporale, Jill, Biofeedback; For the Young and Future Generations, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Caporale, Jill, Nightime Noise Study, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)
  - Carlone, Dennis, Exambook, 1970 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Carragee, Eugene, The Effects of Rotenone treatment on Algae Growth in the Campus Pond, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - Carter, Judy, Litter Baskets for Albany, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - Caruso, Joseph, Civil Disobedience and American Jurisprudence, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Castle, William, Independent Study, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)
  - Cavanaugh, Robert, United States v. MaCarthur, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Cesare, Joseph, Spivack, Alan; Wain, Jackie, Graffiti, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12)
  - Cesari, Antonia, Journal Land Use, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 13)
  - Cesari, Camille, The Bottle and the Bill, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 14)
  - Charton, William, The Sun... A Look at Industries Involvement, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 15)
  - Chase, Jim, Architecture and Energy use, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 16)
  - Chazan, Marc, Stockbroker Liability, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 17)
  - Childers, Ethel, Migrant Labor in NY State, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 18)
  - Cioff Michael, Pesticide Problem and Water Problem, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 19)
  - Clement, Thomas, Exam Book, 1970 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 20)
  - Close, James, Barberville, Falls Charette, 1973 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 21)
  - Cohan, Mike; Maccabee, Bob; Liberman, Mitch, Saratoga Lake: Documenting a Problem, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 22)
  - Cohen, Jeremy, Hering, Thomas Gun Control Legislation, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 23)
  - Cohen, Laurel, A review of my experiences working for the Student Environmental Association, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 24)
  - Cohen, Marge; Spizzo, Vincent The Trans-Alaskan Pipeline, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 25)
  - Colello, Vick,i The Alaskan Pipeline Controversy: Who is Right?, 1973 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 26)
  - Coleman, Mark, A Continuing Humanistic and Realistic look at: Neighborhood Preservation Corporations, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 27)
  - Collins, Marion, Asphalt Man: A textbook of Urban Ecology, 1970 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 28)
  - Collins, Michael, The Newsman's Privilege, 1973 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 29)
  - Comarow, David, Report on Environmental Television Production Project, 1970 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 30)
  - Constantine, Mark, Ornithology Project, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 31)
  - Cook, Gene, Part 1+2, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 32)
  - Coppola, Anthony, Will there be federal action taken to prohibit the use of Aerosol Cans containing Fluorocarbons, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 33)
  - Cortese, Anthony, Analysis of the Impact of Highways on Air Quality, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 34)
  - Corwin, Mary Elle,n No Population Problem? How Dense Canyon Get!, 1973 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 35)
  - Coyne, Dave, SASU Legislative Internship, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 36)
  - Cramer, Kathy, Ann Lee Pond Ecoregion, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 37)
  - Cramer, Keith A Study in Self-Sufficient Housing Albany, NY, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 38)
  - Crampton, John Report on Activities, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 39)
  - Crola, Nancy, The Dangers of Contraception, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 40)
  - Crowell, Edward, No Fault Insurance, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 41)
  - Crusinski, Diane, Pine Bush: Detailed look at Mckown Family Karner Blue Butterfly, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 42)
  - Cuevas, Mathew, Rehabitable Building Survey of Center Square and Hudson Park Neighborhoods, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 43)
  - Cuevas, Matthew, Waterways Project, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 44)
  - Curran, Patrick, Leadership and Student Government, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 45)
  - Czajka, Paul, The Indirect Effect of Coal Production on the Environment throughout History, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 46)
  - Davis, Jackson, Exam, 1970 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 47)
  - Davis, Jackson, 1970 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 48)
  - Davis, Warren, On the Technology and the Economies of Steel Can Recycling in the Steel Industry, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 49)
  - Dawkins, John, Franconere, Vincent, Carbon Monoxide, and Energy and the Environment, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 50)
  - Decker, Ronald, Local Government -- Can It Handle Today's Land use Problems, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 51)
  - Decker, Ronald, Olympic Village, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 52)
  - Decker, Ronald, US Coastal Zone Management an Evaluation, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 53)
  - DeGennaro, Ellen; Teevan, Jan; Stoller, Jon Results of Farming Experiment, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 54)
  - Del Giorno, John, An Air Pollution Case Study; the United States Steel Corporation and the United States, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 55)
  - Deluria, Elaine and others Conservation Film Review, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 56)
  - DeMaso, Tony, Vegetation Along the Hudson River in Albany + Rensselaer Counties, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 57)
  - Deming, Margaret Independent Study, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 58)
  - Deming, Margaret A Week with Isaac Asimov, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 59)
  - DeVesty, Willie Thermal Pollution of Aquatic Systems, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 60)
  - Devlin, Michael, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 61)
  - Dewey, Kay and others Film Reviews, 1971 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 62)
  - Diamond, Howard, Revised Progress an Activity Report from the Issac Truax Jr. Site, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 63)
  - Dicaprio, Joseph Face To Faceless, 1971 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 64)
  - Dickey, Brian A Report on Air and Water Pollution, 1970 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 65)
  - DiMeo, Steve Returnable Bottle Issue, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 66)
  - Dinerstein, Barry Morningside Park, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 67)
  - Di Novo, Jean, Methodology To Produce a Wildlife Habitat Inventory, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 68)
  - Di Nova, Jean; Larkin, Rob; Keleshian, George; Horse Trails in the Pine Bush, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 69)
  - Dissosway, C.F. R., Hop Frog, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 70)
  - Dizard, Ann, Air Pollution, Selkirk, NY, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 71)
  - Doerner, Jeffrey, Bisulfite Catalysed Transamination of Nucleosides, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 72)
  - Dolan, Bill, Journal Waterways, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 73)
  - Donlon, Dennis, The Automobile and the Environment, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 74)
  - Donohue, Kathleen, The Albany Pine Bush Area, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 75)
  - Donovan, William, Architectual and Historical Resources Survey, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 76)
  - Dorrance, Lee, The Effects of Acid Precipitation on Ecosystems, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 77)
  - Dorrance, Lee, Family Planning and Sex Education Information as Forms of Population Control, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 78)
  - Dorrance, Lee, The Tuna Porpoise Problem, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 79)
  - Dorrance, Lee, Environmental Education in Nursery Schools, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 80)
  - Dotz, Robin, Slides, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 81)
  - Doundoulakis, James, The Watergate Affair, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 82)
  - Dowd, Robert, Landuse Controls in the towns of Rockland County, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 83)
  - Doyle, Kathie, Lead Pollution, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 84)
  - Droel, Mari,e Assembly Intern Program, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 85)
  - Duell, Christine, A Study of Peebles Island, Undated (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 86)
  - Duff, Robert, Kirlian Photography Asian Environmental Stress Indicator, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 87)
  - Duren, Mark, Adirondack State Park, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Student Writings), Folder 88)
  - Edelman, Richard; Piranian, Michael; Weiner, Howard, Residence Preference Survey, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - Eden Edward; Eder, Lanny; Rothenberg, Karen, A Look at the Methods and Implications of Water Desalination, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - Egerman, Greg and Rhonda Goodman, Environmental Prospects of the 1980 Winter Olympics, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Elias, Alvin, Composting, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Ellish, Nancy, Independent Study, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)